(this.webpackJsonpmotto=this.webpackJsonpmotto||[]).push([[83,86,102,129,130],{237:function(e,t,s){"use strict";s.r(t),s.d(t,"general",(function(){return n})),s.d(t,"bookSession",(function(){return i})),s.d(t,"socialSession",(function(){return a})),s.d(t,"billing",(function(){return r})),s.d(t,"locations",(function(){return o})),s.d(t,"manageSession",(function(){return m}));var n=[{question:"Why should I use a personal trainer?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"Do I have to belong to the gym in order to book a session?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"How do I know my trainer will be good?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"Do you offer complimentary sessions or consultations?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"If I don\u2019t speak to anybody before I book, how do I know that the trainer will be prepared for my session?",answer:"After booking your session, you will be connected to your trainer through Motto\u2019s messaging system integrated within the platform. Your trainer will reach out to you to ensure they are fully prepared for your session. Likewise, you will be able to ask them any questions you have, or to share/confirm details your trainer may need to know. If you\u2019re unhappy with your trainer selection for any reason, you\u2019ll have until 24 hours before your session to cancel & book another."},{question:"How much do trainers cost?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"How long do sessions last?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"Should I tip?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."}],i=[{question:"How do I find a trainer in my city?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"I am located in a different city. Can I still use Motto?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"How do I contact a trainer?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"Can I buy packages to save money?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."}],a=[{question:"What is a Social Session?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"How do I add friends to a Social Session?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"What is a Motto class?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"How do I add friends to a class?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."}],r=[{question:"Will credit card information be stored?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"When will I be charged?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"How do packages work and are they transferable between trainers?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"How do payments for Social Sessions and classes get split?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."}],o=[{question:"What locations can I get trained at?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"How do I know details about the trainers facility?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"If I book a session at My Location, how does the trainer know where to come?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"Is pricing different for each location?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"What about the equipment?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."}],m=[{question:"What about the equipment?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"What if I need to reschedule a session?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"What happens to Social Sessions and Classes if I cancel?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"What if I want to add more friends to a Social Session or Class after booking?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."},{question:"What if I don\u2019t cancel or reschedule within 24 hours or what if I\u2019m a no-show?",answer:"Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem ipsum has been the.All these fields are mandatory."}]},253:function(e,t,s){"use strict";s.r(t);var n=s(6),i=s(2),a=s(237),r=(s(422),s(423),s(710)),o=s(1),m=function(){return Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"hero_banner",children:Object(o.jsx)("h1",{children:"Frequently Asked Questions"})})};function d(e){var t=Object(i.useState)(!1),s=Object(n.a)(t,2),a=s[0],r=s[1],m=e.data,d=m.question,l=m.answer;return Object(o.jsx)(o.Fragment,{children:Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"accordion-wrapper",children:[Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"title_wrapper",children:Object(o.jsx)("h5",{className:"accordion-title ".concat(a?"open":""),onClick:function(){return r(!a)},children:d})}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"accordion-item ".concat(a?"":"collapsed"),children:Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"accordion-content",children:Object(o.jsx)("p",{children:l})})})]})})}t.default=function(){return Object(o.jsx)(o.Fragment,{children:Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"faq_outer_container",children:[Object(o.jsx)(m,{}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"container",children:Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"faq_wrapper",children:Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"data_container",children:[Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"side_menu_contents",children:Object(o.jsx)("nav",{className:"nav active",children:Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"sidebar_left",children:[Object(o.jsx)(r.Link,{to:"general",spy:!0,children:"general"}),Object(o.jsx)(r.Link,{to:"bookSession",spy:!0,children:"booking a session"}),Object(o.jsx)(r.Link,{to:"socialSession",spy:!0,children:"Social sessions & classes"}),Object(o.jsx)(r.Link,{to:"billing",spy:!0,children:"billing"}),Object(o.jsx)(r.Link,{to:"locations",spy:!0,children:"locations & equipment"}),Object(o.jsx)(r.Link,{to:"manageSession",spy:!0,children:"managing a session"})]})})}),Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"sidebar_right",children:[Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"card_item item1",id:"general",children:[Object(o.jsx)("h6",{children:"General"}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{children:a.general.map((function(e){return Object(o.jsx)(d,{data:e})}))})]}),Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"card_item item1",id:"bookSession",children:[Object(o.jsx)("h6",{children:"Booking A Session"}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{children:a.bookSession.map((function(e){return Object(o.jsx)(d,{data:e})}))})]}),Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"card_item item1",id:"socialSession",children:[Object(o.jsx)("h6",{children:"Social Sessions & Classes"}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{children:a.socialSession.map((function(e){return Object(o.jsx)(d,{data:e})}))})]}),Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"card_item item1",id:"billing",children:[Object(o.jsx)("h6",{children:"Billing"}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{children:a.billing.map((function(e){return Object(o.jsx)(d,{data:e})}))})]}),Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"card_item item1",id:"locations",children:[Object(o.jsx)("h6",{children:"Locations & Equipment"}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{children:a.locations.map((function(e){return Object(o.jsx)(d,{data:e})}))})]}),Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"card_item2 item2",id:"manageSession",children:[Object(o.jsx)("h6",{children:"Managing A Session"}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{children:a.manageSession.map((function(e){return Object(o.jsx)(d,{data:e})}))})]})]})]})})})]})})}},271:function(e,t,s){"use strict";s.r(t);var n=s(253),i=(s(2),s(1));t.default=function(){return Object(i.jsx)("div",{children:Object(i.jsx)(n.default,{})})}},422:function(e,t,s){},423:function(e,t,s){}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=83.0f0fdbd8.chunk.js.map